ASHMA AKTER CHANDNI

Dhaka Polli Bidyut Samity – 1, Savar, Dhaka, Bangladesh

+8801976665517 |
chandni.ashma@gmail.com

https://chandni-ashma.github.io/

Water Resources Engineering graduate student, working as a Lecturer in the Department of Civil Engineering at Military Institute of Science and Technology (MIST), Bangladesh. Experienced in GIS based mapping, river and groundwater flow modeling and contaminant transport modeling.

Education

Bangladesh University of Engineering & Technology Master of Science —Water Resources Engineering

Bangladesh University of Engineering & Technology Bachelor of Science —Water Resources Engineering Expected Graduation: December 2021 Current CGPA 3.75 out of 4.00

> October 2018 CGPA: 3.84 out of 4.00

Computer Skills

Engineering: MODFLOW, ArcGIS, Rockworks, HEC-RAS, Matlab, Python, C++, SAP, AutoCAD

Application: MS Word, Excel, Power point

Work Experience

Lecturer, Department of Civil Engineering, Military Institute of Science and Technology (MIST), Dhaka, Bangladesh.

March 2021 – Current

Lecturer, Department of Civil Engineering, Presidency University, Dhaka, Bangladesh.

May 2019 – Feb 2021

Intern, Bangladesh Water Development Board

March 2018

Research Experience

Master's Thesis: Assessing groundwater flow and nitrate concentration in the south western zone of Bangladesh using MODFLOW

Nov 2020 – Current

-Using Rockworks for preparing stratigraphy and Visual MODFLOW Flex coupled with MT3DMS for flow and transport modeling.

Undergrad Thesis: A GIS-based DRASTIC model for assessing groundwater vulnerability in Magura and Narail districts of Bangladesh

- DRASTIC method has been used to find out contamination vulnerability potential in terms of non-agricultural contaminant.

- Using ArcGIS for the spatial analysis

Jan 2018 – Sept 2018

Govt. Project: Feasibility Study of Excavation and development of 100-ft wide Khal along the both side of Purbachal link road (from Kuril to Balu river)

March 2021 - Present

Course project: Project on Water Quality Parameter Testing of Drinking Water from Ramna Park, Dhaka

August 2017

Course Project: Preparation of 2D models in HEC-RAS for hypothetical test cases

October 2020

Publications

Conference proceedings

Chandni A. A., Rahman A., Yunus A. "Application of DRASTIC Method for Assessing Aquifer Vulnerability of Magura District of Bangladesh Using ArcGIS", 7th International Conference on Water and Flood Management - ICWFM 2019. ISBN: 978-984-34-6192-2, p. 165-166.

Involvements and Awards

- Dean's list scholarship from BUET
- University Merit Scholarship from BUET
- University Stipend from BUET
- Membership: Badhan BUET Zone (former), BUET Self Defense Club (former), Water Resources Engineering Student Association (WRESA)
- Former Child Journalist of Mass-Line Media Center